skwirk.com 2013-05-26

# Year 10, NSW | Online Education Home Schooling Skwirk Australia

## SECTION ONE

Information, held by skwirk.com.au under this Privacy Policy, may be released to entities other than the subject of the information, specifically to:

  1. Third parties engaged to collect debts, or research, or sales and marketing
  2. Third parties authorised by users and members to receive information
  3. Other third parties, as required by law, including, where under warrant, law enforcement agencies

## SECTION TWO

Information for actual or anticipated collection

skwirk.com.au collects or may collect the following kinds of information about members:

  1. Contact information, including an email address nominated as a primary contact email address. It may also include a full name, address and telephone numbers. This information is collected as part of the member registration process and is provided by users.
  2. Personal information, including, but not limited to, age, gender, nationality, suburb or location, sporting affiliations and other interests. This information is provided by members and can be altered.
  3. Any correspondence involving use of the website (including, but not limited to, emails) between users.
  4. Other personal information provided through competitions, survey, or other like activities.
  5. Emailed comments and/or opinions of other members or site visitors that are fairly categorized as feedback or comment.
  6. Non-personally identifiable information, such as your IP address, browser type, pages visited etc. None of this information identifies a user personally

## SECTION THREE

In what manner information, having been collected, is to be used

Information is most regularly used to:

  1. Provide products or services requested by users
  2. Help management of the website
  3. Communicate with members and users
  4. Provide updated information about opportunities in which there is reason to believe that a user be interested
  5. Provide newsletters and updates
  6. Review personal information provided, which is used to review and improve offered services
  7. Record the substance of any complaint, which may be recorded and details stored in case of future complaints against the same user or member.
  8. Collate data for business development purposes
  9. All material provided to users and members, from the information held by skwirk.com.au shall be equipped with an öðpt-out?link to facilitate removal from the list

## SECTION FOUR

Storage of information held by skwirk.com.au

  1. All information is stored on secure systems. Safeguards including physical, technical (firewalls, SSL encryptions etc) and procedural methods are used to protect this data.
  2. Communications and postings, including those with other members are deleted from the systems on a regular basis.
  3. Other personal information provided, voluntarily, in response to contests, surveys, and competitions is deleted on a regular basis after the completion of the event.
  4. Testimonials, complaints and other feedback are stored indefinitely
  5. Update information is available on the website, and enquiries can always be made at [info@skwirk.com.au](mailto:info@skwirk.com.au).

## SECTION FIVE

Enquiring about information held

In general, all requests about information held should be directed to the email address [info@skwirk.com.au](mailto:privacy@skwirk.com.au)

A reply shall be sent with all reasonable speed.

 **Telephone** contact is available at (+612) 9438 3637

 **Postal address is:**|  Skwirk.com.au  
Suite 203  
52 Atchison Street  
St Leonards  
NSW 2065  
---|---  
  
## SECTION SIX

Complaints

  1. Complaints about users may result in the complained of user being contacted. The identity of the complainant, however, shall not be released without prior consent.
  2. Action shall only be taken upon receipt of a written complaint that is substantiated by evidence capable of sustaining the complaint.
  3. All complaints deemed sustained shall be put to the user complained of for an explanation, the result of which may be communicated to the complainant if skwirk.com.au deems that it is reasonably necessary to do so.
  4. Complaints that are upheld shall, if a breach of the terms of use has occurred, result in action, including but not limited to suspension or cancellation of any privileges, to be taken at the discretion of skwirk.com.au, subject to any binding agreements on any of the parties involved

## SECTION SEVEN

Access to information

Persons employed by skwirk.com.au (including sub-contractors) shall access information held by skwirk.com.au under the following restrictions:

  1. They will not use personal contact information or other personal information held by skwirk.com.au for any purpose other than the performance of their jobs.
  2. If they wish to contact a skwirk.com.au user or member, contact shall be made via email at no cost or inconvenience to the skwirk.com.au user or member.
  3. When contact is made by skwirk.com.au with a user or member, such contact will identify itself as representing skwirk.com.au
